{
      "questions": [
{
    "id": 1,
    "type": "true_false",
    "question": "Eclipse is an IDE for Java.",
    "answer": "true",
    "choices": ["true", "false"],
    "feedback": "Eclipse is one of the most well known IDEs not only for Java but for other familiar languages like C, C++, PHP, Ruby, etc."
  },
{
      "id": 2,
      "type": "MC",
      "question": "Which programming language is used for web development?", 
      "answer": "HTML",
      "choices": ["SQL", "Bootstrap", "HTML", "All of the above"],
      "feedback": "HTML is mostly used for displaying information/data on a webpage on the Internet. (SQL focuses on the management of databases and Bootstrap is one of the ways to style an HTML page)." 
  },
{ 
      "id": 3,
      "type": "MC",
      "question": "What does HTML stand for?",
      "answer": "Hypertext Markup Language",
      "choices": ["Highlight Machine Language", "Hightext Machine Language", "Hypertext Makeup Language", "Hypertext Markup Language"]
      "feedback": "HTML stands for Hypertext Markup Language which was created by Tim Berners-Lee."
  },
{
    "id": 4,
    "type": "MC",
    "question": "What is the purpose of CSS?",
    "answer": "To style an HTML webpage",
    "choices": ["To brag to someone that you know CSS", "To store values throughout the HTML webpage", "To style an HTML webpage", "All of the above"]
    "feedback": "CSS (Cascading 
  },
{
    "id": 5,
    "type": "MC",
    "question": "How do you link a Javascript file into an HTML project? (please choose the corresponding line of code)",
    "answer": "<script src = \"JavaScript.js\"> </script>",
    "choices": ["<script src = \"JavaScript.js\">", "<script src = \"JavaScript.js\"> </script>", "<script src = \"JavaScript.js\" </script>", "<script src = Javascript.js> </script>"] 
  },
{
    "id": 6,
    "type": "true_false",
    "question": "Bootstrap is an effective way of styling an HTML webpage.",
    "answer": "true",
    "choices": ["true", "false"]
  },
{
    "id": 7,
    "type": "MC",
    "question": "The SQL programming language focuses on: ",
    "answer": "databases",
    "choices": ["databases", "styling", "development", "none of the above"]
  },
{
    "id": 8,
    "type": "true_false",
    "question": "Tableau allows the user to create a 3D representation of a certain dataset.",
    "answer": "true",
    "choices": ["true", "false"]
  },
{
    "id": 9,
    "type": "MC",
    "question": "What are the data types that displays whole number values in Java?",
    "answer": "int",
    "choices": ["int", "double", "string", "boolean"]
  },
 {
    "id": 10,
    "type": "MC",
    "question": "Which of the following is a type of loop in Java?",
    "answer": "all of the above",
    "choices": ["For", "While", "Do-while", "all of the above"]
  },
 {
    "id": 11,
    "type": "true_false",
    "question": "Python is a high level, interpreted, interactive, and object-oriented scripting language.",
    "answer": "true",
    "choices": ["true", "false"]
  },
{
    "id": 12,
    "type" : "text",
    "question" : "Type a print statement for Python below (let the string be \"Hello World\"):",
    "answer" : "print(\"Hello World\")",
    "choices" : "answer_to_question"
},
{
    "id": 13,
    "type" : "text",
    "question" : "Type the HTML5 declaration statement below:",
    "answer" : "<!DOCTYPE html>",
    "choices" : "answer_to_question"
},
{
    "id": 14,
    "type" : "text",
    "question" : "What does the \"import java.util.Scanner;\" add to a Java program?",
    "answer" : "a scanner",
    "choices" : "answer_to_question"
},
{
    "id": 15,
    "type" : "text",
    "question" : "What does DDoS stand for?",
    "answer" : "Distributed Denial of Service",
    "choices" : "answer_to_question"
},
{
    "id": 16,
    "type" : "text",
    "question" : "Type the HTML snippet that links a CSS file to an HTML file (name the CSS file \"CSS_styling.css\"): ",
    "answer" : "<link rel=\"stylesheet\" href=\"CSS_styling.css\">",
    "choices" : "answer_to_question"
},
{
    "id": 17,
    "type" : "text",
    "question" : "How many times does this loop run?    int i = 0;  while (i < 10) {  System.out.println(i);  i++;  }",
    "answer" : "10",
    "choices" : "answer_to_question"
},
{
    "id": 18,
    "type" : "text",
    "question" : "What SQL command allows the user to create a new database? (type the command in all caps)",
    "answer" : "CREATE DATABASE",
    "choices" : "answer_to_question"
},
{
    "id": 19,
    "type" : "text",
    "question" : "Which version of Bootstrap have we been using throughout this class? (type in the number)",
    "answer" : "4",
    "choices" : "answer_to_question"
},
{
    "id": 20,
    "type" : "text",
    "question" : "Find the index of \"BMW\" in the array: [\"MINI\", \"Mercedes-Benz\", \"Audi\", \"Chevrolet\", \"Ford\", \"BMW\", \"Fiat\", \"Dodge\"]",
    "answer" : "5",
    "choices" : "answer_to_question"
},
{
    "id": 21,
    "type" : "text",
    "question" : "What is the maximum amount of columns that the Bootstrap 4 grid system allows? (type in the number)",
    "answer" : "12",
    "choices" : "answer_to_question"
}
 ]
}
  



